Okay, so now let's talk about
Cloud Integration.
So when we have multiple applications,
at some point they will have to communicate
with one another.
And there are two types of patterns
to make applications communicate.
The first one is easy to understand,
it's called a synchronous communication
in which an application talks to another application.
For example, you have created a service to buy something
and then you need to talk to a service
that ships what has been bought.
And so therefore you want to integrate the buying service
and the shipping service synchronously
because it talk directly to one another.
That's the first way, but there's a second way,
which is called asynchronous or event based,
for example when we have a queue to talk to.
So let's have an example,
our buying service this time, anytime something is bought,
will put an order in a queue.
And the shipping service will be reading
from the queue to get the orders.
As you can see in this example,
your buying service and your shipping service
are not directly integrated with one another.
There are something called decoupled
because there is a queue in between to talk to.
And this allows us to get some nice integration patterns.
So if we get synchronous communication
between an application and another one,
it could be a problem.
For example, what if you have a sudden spike of traffic?
What if you need to encode 1000 videos, but usually it's 10?
In this case, the service you are talking to
may get overwhelmed and you may get an issue
to encode these 1000 videos and things may fail.
In that case.
It's a lot better to decouple your applications
and to use something like SQS, which is a queue model,
or SNS, which is a pub/sub model,
or Kinesis, which is used for real time data streaming.
Now these services, once they're decoupled,
they can scale independently for our applications.
And so this is great.
So in this section,
we're going to have a deeper look at SQS and SNS.
So I hope you like this
and I will see you in the next lecture.